foodzie.com 2011-12-23

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers the use of the web site located at http://foodzie.com and the services provided by Foodzie, Inc. ("Foodzie"), including how Foodzie treats personal information that Foodzie collects and receives. Pursuant to Foodzie's Terms of Use, you must be 18 years and older to use this site or have permission from a legal guardian. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 18 years old. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Foodzie does not own or control, or individuals that Foodzie does not employ or manage. This policy is effective on September 1, 2009. 

**General Information:**  
• Foodzie will not sell or disclose your name or email address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.  
• Foodzie collects personal information when you register to use Foodzie services or to post content on Foodzie. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information.  
• If you would like to obtain a Seller account, Foodzie will ask for your business address, phone number, and payment information.  
• Foodzie automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.  
• Foodzie uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in Foodzie's user registration databases when you register with Foodzie. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes, and/or delivering unique functionality in the Foodzie Marketplace.  

Foodzie will send you a welcome email when you sign up for Foodzie's services. 

Foodzie will send you service announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. 

You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing [support@foodzie.com](mailto:support@foodzie.com) from the email address you signed up with.

Foodzie may periodically email you with administrative messages. Foodzie will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your information may be combined with information Foodzie collects from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive administrative messages or participate in these programs, simply opt-out by emailing [support@foodzie.com.](mailto:support@foodzie.com)

If you no longer wish to receive administrative messages, you may opt-out by emailing [support@foodzie.com.](mailto:support@foodzie.com) Please note that if you do not wish to receive administrative messages from us, those notices will still govern your use of the Foodzie website and service, and you are responsible for reviewing such notices for changes.  
**Password:** Keep your password secure. You are fully responsible for all activity, liability and damage resulting from your failure to maintain password confidentiality. You agree to immediately notify Foodzie of any unauthorized use of your password or any breach of security. You also agree that Foodzie cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to keep your password secure. 

**Account Information:** You must keep your account information up-to-date and accurate at all times, including a valid email address. 

**Account Transfer:** You may not transfer or sell your Foodzie account and User ID to another party. If you are registering as a business entity, you personally guarantee that you have the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.

Foodzie offers subscriptions to Foodzie email newsletters. To opt-in, Foodzie will ask for your email address and the newsletter(s) you wish to receive. This email address will only be used for this feature. You may change your subscription or unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained in the email.

"Share with a Friend" allows members to share information about a seller or a specific item listed on Foodzie by sending a personalized email message. 

If you choose to use Foodzie's "Share with a Friend" feature, Foodzie will ask for the information needed to send the message, such as your friend's email address. Foodzie will then automatically send your friend an email, inviting your friend to visit the site. Foodzie does not store "Share with a Friend" information on our servers.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Foodzie service. Foodzie uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Foodzie's services; display local product offerings; estimate and report Foodzie's total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve Foodzie's content and services. Foodzie cookies do not collect personal information, and Foodzie does not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or email address is.

When you post a message, your Foodzie ID or alias is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Foodzie may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Foodzie Terms of Use. Foodzie may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with Foodzie's Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy, as Foodzie in Foodzie's sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, Foodzie may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. Foodzie may share aggregated demographic information with business partners. 

Foodzie is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them. These businesses may operate stores on the Foodzie website or sell items to you from the Foodzie website. Foodzie may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. Due to the nature of Foodzie's business model, when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, you will share customer information that is related to such transaction with that affiliated business. 

Foodzie employs other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and needs to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, handling billing disputes, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. 

Foodzie will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Foodzie has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Foodzie's Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. In some cases, Foodzie may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Foodzie will transfer information about you if Foodzie is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Foodzie will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Foodzie web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

As part of the buying and selling process, you may obtain another Foodzie user's email address, shipping address and/or other information. Pursuant to Foodzie's Terms of Use, you have a limited license to use this information. This information should only be used for Foodzie-related communications or for Foodzie-facilitated transactions. Foodzie has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Foodzie user to your email or physical mail list.

If you use a forum on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others or could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Foodzie is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information Foodzie collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on Foodzie or throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Foodzie does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. Foodzie is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the Foodzie site. Foodzie encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

You can change your Foodzie Account Information (except your username), at any time. Foodzie may send you certain communications relating to the Foodzie service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Foodzie account. You can delete your Foodzie account by emailing [support@foodzie.com](mailto:support@foodzie.com). Please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Foodzie's records for some period. 

Foodzie limits access to personal information about you to employees who Foodzie believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Foodzie Account Information is password-protected. 

If your personally identifiable information changes you may correct or update it by making the change on your Foodzie account page. You may delete or deactivate your account by emailing Customer Support at [support@foodzie.com](mailto:support@foodzie.com). Foodzie will respond to your request within 10-20 business days.

The security of your personal information is important to us. Your Foodzie account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) for registration Foodzie encrypts that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Foodzie follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Foodzie receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Foodzie strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Foodzie cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Foodzie's Web site, you can email Foodzie at [support@foodzie.com](mailto:support@foodzie.com).

If this privacy policy is changed, Foodzie will post changes so that you are aware of those changes. Foodzie reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If Foodzie makes material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places Foodzie deems appropriate.

If you have questions or suggestions you can submit them to [support@foodzie.com](mailto:support@foodzie.com) or by postal mail to Foodzie Attn: Customer Support; 164 Townsend St, Unit 1, San Francisco, CA 94107.
